You've got a lotta nerve
to say you are my friend
When I was down you just
stood there grinnin'
You've got a lotta nerve to say
you got a helping hand to lend
You just want to be on
the side that's winnin'
You say I let you down,
ya know its not like that
If you're so hurt,
why then don't you show it?
You say you've lost your faith,
but that's not where its at
You have no faith to lose,
and ya know it
I know the reason, that you
talked behind my back
I used to be among the crowd
you're in with
Do you take me for such a fool,
to think I'd make contact
With the one who tries to hide
what he don't know
to begin with?
You see me on the street,
you always act surprised
You say "how are you?", "good
luck", but ya don't mean it
When you know as well as me,
you'd rather see me paralyzed
Why don't you just come out
once and scream it
No, I do not feel that good
when I see the heartbreaks
you embrace
If I was a master thief
perhaps I'd rob them
And tho I know
you're dissatisfied
with your position
and your place
Don't you understand,
its not my problem?
I wish that for just one time
you could stand inside my shoes
And just for that one moment
I could be you
Yes, I wish that for
just one time
you could stand inside my shoes
You'd know what a drag
it is to see you